watermarquee.com 2019-07-16

# Privacy Policy | Watermarquee

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Water Marquee collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Water Marquee’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Water Marquee’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Water Marquee may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

Water Marquee also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. Water Marquee only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below. 

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Water Marquee’s websites choose to interact with Water Marquee in ways that require Water Marquee to gather personally-identifying information. Visitors who sign up to use Water Marquee must provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with Water Marquee – by purchasing a paid plan – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Water Marquee collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Water Marquee. Water Marquee does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

## Aggregated Statistics

Water Marquee may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. For instance, Water Marquee may monitor usage patterns to different plan types in order to properly scale the service. Water Marquee may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Water Marquee does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Water Marquee discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Water Marquee's behalf or to provide services available at Water Marquee’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Water Marquee’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Water Marquee will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Water Marquee discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Water Marquee believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Water Marquee, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Water Marquee website and have supplied your email address, Water Marquee may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Water Marquee. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Water Marquee takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Water Marquee uses cookies to help Water Marquee identify and track visitors, their usage of the Water Marquee website, and their website access preferences. Water Marquee visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Water Marquee’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Water Marquee’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

## Business Transfers

If Water Marquee, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Water Marquee goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Water Marquee may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Water Marquee may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Water Marquee’s sole discretion. Water Marquee encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
